MD. MOMINUL ISLAM

Address: N/A, Tangail Sadar, Tangail Sadar, Tangail 1900

Primary Mobile No: 01710650617 Secondary Mobile No: 01817000622 Emergency Contact No: 01721082789 Primary Email: msobus@gmail.com



Career Objective:

I want to find a position where I can improve my business activities and can contribute on the particular marketing sector. I am hard working, self-motivated and enthusiastic. Moreover, I can work under pressure and can take challenge.

Career Summary:

B2B and B2C sales and marketing specialist with over 7 years of experience in sales, marketing, brand management and customer relationship management. Experienced in working with team to overcome challenges and beat KPIs. Smart working and quick learning individual in Bangladesh

Special Qualification:

I am very energetic and dedicated to office work. I am regular and know the very basic of your required field. I have 7 years of experience in the Markating And Sales field I think I am the best candidate for your Job post.

Employment History:

Total Year of Experience: 10.1 yrs

1. Senior Executive (0.3 yr)

(May, 2022 - Continuing)

Summit communications Ltd

Dhaka. Posting: Tangail

Area of Expertise

Sales & Marketing (0 yr)

Duties/Responsibilities

- On-boarding new clients by analyzing the potentiality and business prospect - To collaborate with clients & technical team on customer requirements, prepare end-to-end project plan with project management team & follow up with planning/implementation/project team regarding the delivery of service. - Ensuring regular client visits and correspondences to achieve a set of KPI targets & ensure an accurate database adherence to company set compliance - Coordinating with the service and support team to ensure customer satisfaction. - Created promotional offers and strategies to attain new requirements, and new businesses by conducting a survey on existing ISPs (Internet Service Provider) clients to meet trade marketing objectives of the company. - Managing key accounts Of Regional ISP , and bought new businesses from the existing client through effective communication and personal rapport - Co-ordinate with the operators` regulatory authorities & maintain close communication with internal regulatory team - Ensuring proper collection of bills from the client by following up with the Client BR

2. Territory Sales Executive (MIME - ISP) (1.7 yrs)

(September, 2020 - May, 2022)

Digicon Telecommunications Ltd

15th Floor, Awal Center, 34, Kemal Attaturk Avenue Banani Commercial Area, Dhaka-1213

Area of Expertise

Sales & Marketing (0.8 yr)

Duties/Responsibilities

Job ResponsibilitiesBRResponsible for generating new sales.BRAchieving monthly, quarterly and annual sales target.BRTo maintain relationship with the existing and new customers.BRPromote MiME internet as a brand.BROrganizing regular field visits to prospective clients, demonstrating and presenting our work and establishing new businesses & products.BRResponsible for all necessary activity set by management in assigned districts.BRShare monthly competitor analysis report.BRWorking with the field marketing team to develop targeted sales strategies.BRTracking sales data to ensure the company meets sales quotas.BRCollecting data from field for product and business development.BRExplore new markets to contribute in sales increase.

3. Marketing Promotion Officer, Marketing And Sales (1.6 yrs)

(December, 2018 - July, 2020)

Fiber@Home Ltd

House # 7/B, Road # 13 Gulshan-1, Dhaka-1212

Area of Expertise

Marketing (0.5 yr), Marketing Promotion (0.5 yr), Sales & Marketing (0.5 yr)

Duties/Responsibilities

Preparing, planning and managing the regional campaign of Tangail, Manikganj region to maximize Fiber@Home brand promotion.

Execute marketing campaigns and working with the Marketing Key Accounts Manager to see them executed.

Developing new innovative ways to communicate the company message to regional customers.

Acquiring and developing new customers

Meet the Monthly sales target.

Planning and managing regional marketing events and evaluating their success.

Evaluating the effectiveness of all marketing activity for his assigned region & report to head office accordingly.

Implementing an internal marketing program.

Supporting the Line manager in day to day marketing activities.

Develop and deliver campaigns as agreed within timescales.

Support finance team to collect bill from client (Monthly Basis).

Support operation team for site survey/client communication/Site access related issues.

4. Executive -Customer Service (Client Service) (2.9 yrs)

(January, 2016 - December, 2018)

Contessa Solutions & Consultants Ltd

House No: 450 Road No: 31 (1st Floor) Mohakhali New DOHS Dhaka-1206, Bangladesh

Area of Expertise

Marketing (1.4 yrs), Sales (1.4 yrs)

Duties/Responsibilities

Achieve company revenue and profit target with proper planning and execution.

Planning and implementing sales and business development strategies.

Identifying key areas for improvement in the sales process.

Create new customer and following up with existing customer.

Maintain and develop relationship with various stakeholders.

Identifying potential market/clients along with new sales opportunity.

Monthly reporting on sales performance against budget and reporting on variances

5. Field Superviser (Part Time), Tangail (2.8 yrs)

(September, 2012 - June, 2015)

Market Access Providers Limited

Gulshan, Dhaka

Area of Expertise

Business Development (0.9 yr), Event/ Campaign Co-ordinator (0.9 yr), Sales & Marketing (0.9 yr)

Duties/Responsibilities

Various Project Marketing Campaign in Tangail, Local HR Recruitment & Event Management Support.: 1. Trade Marketing for Airtel launching program in Tangail territory.

- 2. Brand Marketing For Various Company on Tangail Like as Banglalink, Unilever, Nokia, Britist Ameracian Tobaco etc.
- 3. Trade Marketing For Various Company on Tangail Like as Banglalink, Unilever, Nokia, Britist Ameracian Tobaco etc.

6. Business Development Officer (Contractual) (0.4 yr)

(December, 2011 - May, 2012)

Banglalink

Regional Office, 7 no. College Road, Mymensingh, Bangladesh

Area of Expertise

Marketing (0.2 yr), Sales (0.2 yr)

Duties/Responsibilities

1. Banglalink SME Corporate SIM Sales & Marketing.

Academic Qualification:

Exam Title	Concentration/Major	Institute	Result	Pas.Year	Duration
Master of Business Administration (MBA)	Marketing	Bangladesh Open University	Appeared	2022	2
Bachelor of Business Studies (BBS)	Marketing	Govt: Chowhali College (National University)	Second Class, Marks :50%	2012	3YAER
H.S.C(BM)	Secretarial Science	Monjur Kader Technical School And College	CGPA:3.98 out of 5	2009	2 YEAR
SSC	Science	KHAS KAWALIA K. R. PILOT HIGH SCHOOL	CGPA:2.38 out of 5	2003	10 YEAR

Training Summary:

Training Title	Topic	Institute	Country	Location	Year	Duration
Cyber Security : Do your part, be cyber	Cyber Security : Do your part, be cyber	organized by Gen Lab and US	Bangladesh	Online	2021	6day
smart	smart	Embassy				
The Training on "Basic MS Word and Excel."	: Excel Introduction with Excel : Effective Data Managing Skill : Effective Formatting : Mostly Used buttons, tools and tip: Cell References : Basic Formula & Functions	CONFIDENCE GROUP	Bangladesh	Zoom Online	2020	4 day

Professional Qualification:

Certification	Institute	Location	From	То
National Skill Standard Basic Certificate Course Computer Office Application	Bangladesh Technical Education Board	Tangail	July 1, 2020	December 31, 2021

Career and Application Information:

Looking For : Mid Level Job Available For : Full Time Present Salary : Tk. 40000 Expected Salary : Tk. 60000

Preferred Job Category : General Management/Admin, IT/Telecommunication, Marketing/Sales

Preferred District : Dhaka, Manikganj, Sirajganj, Tangail

Preferred Country : Canada, United Arab Emirates, United Kingdom, United States

Preferred Organization Types : Telecommunication, Manufacturing (FMCG), Event Management, IT Enabled Service,

ISP, Multinational Companies, Technical Infrastructure

Specialization:

Fields of Specialization

Sales & Marketing

- Corporate Sales and Marketing
- Technical Sales/ IT Marketing
- IT & Software Marketing
- Telecommunication Products & Services

Extra Curricular Activities:

I have achieved 3 medals at inter-school cricket tournament.

I have achieved sale target and 1st all over the Fiber@Home business development team

Language Proficiency:

Language	Reading	Writing	Speaking
BANGLA	High	High	High
English	Medium	Medium	Medium

Personal Details :

Father's Name : MD. ABDUL KARIM TALUKDER

Mother's Name : MST. SALINA AKTER Date of Birth : September 25, 1987

Gender : Male

Height (Meter)

Weight (Kg) :

Marital Status : Single
Nationality : Bangladeshis
National Id No. : 9317614043360

Religion : Islam
Passport No : EF0397844
Passport Issue Date : 12/31/2020

Permanent Address : Khas Shajani Nagarpur, Nagarpur, Nagarpur, Tangail 1936

Current Location : Tangail Blood Group : O+

Disability ID : 931761404336002

I have some difficulties which are given below

- Seeing (Yes some difficulty)
- **Physical** (Yes some difficulty)

Reference (s):

Address

Reference: 01

Name : Md. Shohal

Organization : Bangladesh Telecommunication Regulatory

Commission

Designation : Parsonal offices

Bangladesh Telecommunication Regulatory

: Commission (BTRC) IEB Bhaban (5,6 &~7

floor) Ramna, Dhaka-1000

Phone (Off.) : +8801550080214

Phone (Res.)

Mobile : 01911264039

E-Mail : mdsohel@btrc.gov.bd

Relation : Others

Reference: 02

Md. Tamim Salehin

DigiCon Telecommunication Ltd

Manager, Marketing & Sales

15th Floor, Awal Center, 34, Kemal Attaturk Avenue Banani Commercial Area, Dhaka-1213

+88-01704119671

tamim.salehin@cg-bd.com

Professional